retale.com 2014-11-02

# Retale: Privacy Policy

#### Effective Date : October 7th, 2013 (last updated April 25th, 2014) 

## This Privacy Policy applies to our sites and apps.

This Policy describes how we treat personal information on the websites where it is located. This includes www.retale.com. It also applies to our mobile sites and apps. 

## We collect information from and about you.

**\- Contact information.** For example, we might collect your email address if you sign up for our emails. 

**\- Information you submit or post.** For example, we collect the information you post in a public space on our website. We also collect information if you respond to a survey. 

**\- Demographic information.** We may collect your zip code to help you find sales relevant to you. 

**\- Other information.** If you use our website, we may collect information about your IP address and the browser you’re using. We might look at what site you came from, or what site you visit when you leave us. If you use our mobile app, we may collect your GPS location. We might look at how often you use the app and where you downloaded it. We collect this information using the tracking tools described [here](http://www.retale.com/ads-and-tracking). To control these tools, please [read here.](http://www.retale.com/ads-and-tracking)

## We collect information in different ways.

**\- We collect information directly from you.** For example, if you sign up for alerts.   

**\- We collect information from you passively.** We use tracking tools like browser cookies and web beacons to collect information from you. Learn more about these tools, and how you can control them, [here](http://www.retale.com/ads-and-tracking).   

**\- We get information about you from third parties.** For example, our business partners may give us information about you. Social media platforms may also give us information about you. 

## We use information as disclosed and described here.

**\- We use information to respond to your requests or questions.** For example, we might use your information to respond to your comments or questions. 

**\- We use information to improve our products and services.** We may use your information to make our website and products better. We might use your information to customize your experience with us. We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get from third parties. 

**\- We use information for security purposes.** We may use information to protect our company, our customers, and our websites. 

**\- We use information for marketing purposes.** For example, we might send you information about special offers. We might tell you about new features or updates. 

**\- We use information to communicate with you about your account or our relationship.** We may contact you about your account or feedback. We might also contact you about this Policy or our website Terms. We may also use push notifications on our mobile apps. 

**\- We use information as otherwise permitted by law.**

## We may share information with third parties.

**\- We will share information within the Bonial family of companies.** This includes future subsidiaries or affiliates. 

**\- We will share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf.** For example, we share information with vendors who send emails for us. We may also share information with companies that operate our websites. 

**\- We will share information with our business partners.** For example, we may share information with third parties who operate our “find ads near me” feature. We may also share information with third parties who co-sponsor a promotion. We may also share information with our retail partners. This might include those whose circulars and ads appear on our platforms. 

**\- We will share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves** For example, we will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests. We might share information when we are investigating potential fraud. 

**\- We may share information with any successor to all or part of our business.** For example, if part of our business was sold we may give our customer list as part of that transaction. 

**\- We may share information for other reasons we may describe to you.**

## You have certain choices about sharing and marketing practices.

**You can opt out of receiving our marketing emails.** To stop receiving our promotional emails, follow the instructions in any promotional message you get from us. Don’t worry - even if you opt out of getting marketing messages, we will still send you transactional messages. These include responses to your questions or information about your account. 

**You can control cookies and tracking tools.** To learn how to manage how we – and our vendors – use cookies and other tracking tools, please click [here](http://www.retale.com/ads-and-tracking). 

## Your California Privacy Rights

If you reside in California, you have the right to ask us one time each year if we have shared personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make a request, please send us an [email](mailto:privacy@retale.com), or write to us at the address listed below. Indicate in your letter that you are a California resident making a “Shine the Light” inquiry.

## These sites and children.

Our sites and apps are meant for adults. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can [email us](mailto:privacy@retale.com). You can also write to us at the address listed at the end of this policy. Please mark your inquiries “COPPA Information Request.” Parents, you can learn more about how to protect children's privacy on-line [here](http://www.business.ftc.gov/privacy-and-security/childrens-privacy). 

## We use standard security measures.

The Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our sites will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. This includes not sharing your passwords. We keep personal information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Policy. We also keep information as otherwise required by law. 

## We store information in the United States.

If you live outside of the United States, you understand and agree that we may transfer your information to the United States. This site is subject to U.S. laws, which may not afford the same level of protection as those in your country.

## We may link to other sites or have third party services on our site we don’t control.

If you click on a link to a third party site, you will be taken to websites we do not control. This includes social media sites. This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of these websites. Read the privacy policy of other websites and insurance carriers carefully. We are not responsible for these third party practices. Our site and apps may also link to and/or serve third party ads or other content that contains their own cookies or tracking technologies. To learn more, [click here](http://www.retale.com/ads-and-tracking). We do not control the use of those technologies. 

## Feel free to contact us if you have more questions.

If you have any questions about this Policy, please email us at [privacy@retale.com](mailto:privacy@retale.com). You can also write to us or call at:   
**Retale Consumer Relations**   
525 W Monroe St. Chicago, IL 60661, USA   
Phone: 312-258-8800 

## We may update this Policy.

From time to time we may change our privacy policies. We will notify you of any material changes to our Policy as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on our website. Please check our site periodically for updates. 

© 2014 Bonial Enterprises North America, Inc. All rights reserved.
